# RIAJUL ISLAM

Address : Road No. 1, West Nandipara, South Banasree, Khilgaon, Dhaka 1219

**Phone** : +8801722787007

E-mail : riajul.islam.dev@gmail.com



#### GitHub:

www.github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/riajul-islam-dev

Skype:

join.skype.com/invite/y4awZfHii9yl

Website:

https://riajul-islam-dev.github.io

## **Skill Highlights**

### **Front-end Technologies:**

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax
- Vue.js

### **Back-end Technologies:**

- C, C++, Golang
- PHP, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Laravel, Yii Framework
- ASP.NET Core MVC

#### **Additional Skills:**

Internet of Things (IoT)

### References

#### Dr. Md. Nawab Yousuf Ali

Professor, Department of Computer

Science and Engineering

East West University

Email: nawab@ewubd.edu

Tel: +88 09666775577 Ext. 104

## **Dr. Ahmed Wasif Reza**

Professor, Department of Computer

Science and Engineering

**East West University** 

Email: wasif@ewubd.edu

Tel: +88 09666775577 Ext. 394

#### Web App ASP.NET Core MVC

ASP.NET Core MVC based Web App to purchase

products

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/WebApp ASP.NET Core MVC

#### **IOT Based Project**

**IOT Based Smart Window with Remote Controlling** System

**Git:** https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/IOT-Based-Smart-Window-with-Remote-Controlling-System

## **Career Objective**

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer with a proven track record of solution-focused work and an unwavering commitment to web development. Known for my self-motivation, team-building skills, and consistently delivering best results in this ever-evolving field.

#### Education

### Japanese-language proficiency Level N3

VENTURAS Ltd., Dhaka (May 15, 2022 - Nov 30, 2022)

### **BSc, in Computer Science & Engineering**

East West University, Dhaka (May 2014 - August 2019)

## **Experience**

### **Full Stack Web Developer**

November 2023 - To date

Trust Innovation Limited (TIL), Dhaka Cantonment

**Intern Web Developer (Remote)** 

December 2022 - February 2023

ZUU Co.,Ltd., Japan

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

October 2021 - April 2022

NexKraft Limited, Dhaka

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

May 2022 - October 2023 Leotech BD, Dhaka

**Associate Web Developer** 

September 2020 – October 2021

Perky Rabbit, Dhaka

### **Projects**

#### CaseHub (BRAC's Legal & Compliance Website)

Developed this Website's Phase 3

Link: https://casehub.brac.net

## **Legal Information Management System**

Case & Lawyer Management System for any Organization Git: <a href="https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/lims-skote-laravel-">https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/lims-skote-laravel-</a>

### starterkit

### **Online Shop Yii**

Online Ecommerce Shop in Yii Framework

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/Online Shop Yii

#### **Ecommerce in Laravel**

Ecommerce Management System for any Brand or Company with POS, stock, Employee & Customer management.

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/Arong-Dhong

#### **Academic System in Raw PHP**

Management system for Admin, Teacher, Student & Staff's Profile, Exam & Result system

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-

Dev/PerkyRabbit Result Publishment System